What the ...Go ahead. Slice me.It'll be the last thing you ever do.
搞什么呀 来呀  你咬我啊  它会是你做的最后一件事
-I'm working here, you waste of fur.-Frustrated Diego.
-我在办事  你们这俩饭桶 -倒霉的Diego
-Tracking down helpless infants too difficult for you?-What are you two doing here?
-找个小不点婴儿对你来说太难了 -你们俩来这干嘛
Soto's getting tired of waiting.
索托已经等得不耐烦了
Yeah. Yeah. He said, come back with the baby,
他说要么带着小孩回来
or don't come back at all!
要么就永远别回来了
Well, I have a message for Soto.
替我捎个信给索托
Tell him, I'm bringing the baby.
告诉他  我会带孩子来
And tell him, I'm bringing a mammoth.
再告诉他  我还会带一头长毛象回去
-A mammoth. -Mammoths never travel alone.
-一头长毛象 -长毛象从不单独行动
Well, this one does. And I'm leading him to Half peak.
可这头是例外  我要带他去“半峰”山
Look at all that meat.
瞧他那身肉
Let's get him! Not yet!
捉住它  还不行
We need the whole pack to bring this mammoth down.Get everyone ready.
得叫大伙儿一起上才能摆平他 让大家快准备
Now!
快去